{
    "id": "b0254649413342398940935f64511a12",
    "title": "Degrees Of Comparison",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She was ………………………. than I thought.",
            "description": "We use the comparative form before than.",
            "answers": [
                "tall",
                "taller",
                "tallest"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Although the house was …………………… I bought it.",
            "description": "When there is no idea of comparison we use the positive form of the adjective. ",
            "answers": [
                "small",
                "smaller",
                "smallest"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Is your grandmother any ………………………. today?",
            "description": "The comparative form is used when change is indicated. ",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "better",
                "best"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Russia is …………………………… country in the world.",
            "description": "We use the superlative form of the adjective to compare a person/thing with the whole group to which that person/thing belongs. ",
            "answers": [
                "largest",
                "the largest",
                "the larger",
                "larger"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She is …………………………. wonderful woman I have ever met.",
            "description": "We make the superlative form of wonderful by adding the most. ",
            "answers": [
                "the more",
                "the most",
                "most"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I do ……………………… work than you.",
            "description": "More is the comparative form of much. ",
            "answers": [
                "more",
                "much",
                "most"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She earns ………………………… than her husband.",
            "description": "The comparative is used to compare one person or thing with another person or thing. ",
            "answers": [
                "more",
                "much",
                "most"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We are not as ……………………….. as them.",
            "description": "When there is no idea of comparison, we use the positive adjective. ",
            "answers": [
                "rich",
                "richer",
                "richest"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "That was …………………….. unforgettable experience in my life.",
            "description": "We use the with superlative adjectives. ",
            "answers": [
                "most",
                "the most"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "My sister has ……………………….. voice in my family.",
            "description": "We use the superlative form of the adjective to compare a person/thing with the whole group to which that person/thing belongs. ",
            "answers": [
                "sweet",
                "the sweetest",
                "sweetest"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Which is ……………………….. bird in the world?",
            "description": "We use the superlative form of the adjective to compare a person/thing with the whole group to which that person/thing belongs. ",
            "answers": [
                "the large",
                "the larger",
                "the largest"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Platinum is ……………………… precious metal.",
            "description": "The superlative form of precious is most precious. ",
            "answers": [
                "the more",
                "the most",
                "the preciouest"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}